Thank you for watching!
Be a Sheken!
Aramaya and Momotamoya
A little mistake and unlucky, down! Down!
It happens all the time.
Please wake up chip rape in three, two, one
With a mysterious beat
Dreams I haven't even told my parents
Bigger and bigger and freer than ever
I'll be fine, if it's with you
Sheken up!
The future that no one knows
Our future will open up with our own hands
Let's do it with our hearts full of excitement
Hop, step, sheken up chance
Sheken up!
The power of self-belief
I'm ordinary but determined
Chance has come and gone for me
Up and down!
Be Sheken!
Don't be a Sheken
Sheken, Sheken, Sheken!
By H. R. R.
Hello! Stee, this time we have with us Yuka Saito from Ochanouma and Mika Nishizaki from Ochanouma.
Please stay with us until the end.
Please bear with us until the end.
At the beginning of this article, we would like to introduce the music video short version of "Shekenare" from Ochanouma's 3rd single which will be released on July 26th,
Shekenare music video short version.
Yay!
The song "Shekenare" is the ending song for the TV anime "Shadow Bus Frame".
This song has the keyword "kirifuda" (trump card) in it, which fits perfectly with the anime.
This music video is the first time Ochanouma used a vertical camera to take selfies,
The video is divided into three parts, so it has an atmosphere of Ochanouma delivering the video,
We hope you will enjoy this music video as well.
And this is the first time that I have seen a video of the "Halo! On July 5, when the video is being broadcasted, we will be holding a mini-live at the Ikebukuro Sunshine City Fountain Plaza,
We will be holding a mini-live & omeyaku (understanding) event to commemorate the release of our 3rd single at Sunshine City Fountain Plaza in Ikebukuro on July 5.
So, thank you all for coming.
This 3rd single release event was held from Kagoshima,
What a first release event for Ochanouma with 1,000 yen, how was it? Miku.
It was a lot more fun than I thought it would be,
I was very happy to hear everyone's voices,
I also felt like we were creating the performance together,
I would like to hear more and more voices from now on.
I will talk more about the new single later, so please look forward to it!
Please take a look at this video first.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Now then, what are you all waiting for?
I would like to introduce the 17th term members who just joined us the other day.
I would like to introduce our new 17th term members.
Seventeenth term, come here.
Come here.
Elemental hand
Please introduce yourself.
I am Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto.
The difficult word I have recently learned is "overboard production".
I look forward to working with you.
Cute!
Passing over production, right?
Did you get over it?Did I get overboard?
It's tough, isn't it? Trains, right?
Tokyo is tough, isn't it?
Tokyo, right?
Okay. Okay, let's continue.
I'm Takako Inoue, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
[Applause]
My pride is my sharp radio gymnastics.
Oh, wow.
I'm curious.
I like it.
Even you are curious about it, aren't you?
Right?
You know...
I heard some voices from everyone,
Maybe it was red, because it looked like red,
I thought so, didn't I?
I'll tell you exactly what I'm going to say.
I'll tell you right away.
So, let's hear from the members themselves.
First of all, Haruka-chan.
What is my member color, Haruka Inoue?
Oh, wow.
Mint green.
This is it.
It looks good on you.
It does.
It's nice.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow.
I'm so happy.
That's great.
How's it going? Haruka.
It looks like a rice paddy.
It's not a rice paddy.
It looks like a rice field.
It looks like a rice paddy.
Thank you very much.
That's great. I'm so happy.
Well, go on, then.
Ako-chan, you want to go?
Let's go, Ako-chan.
I, Akiko Ikigen, have a member color,
Pure red.
Quick!
You're early!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to say I was already ready.
How is it? Ako-chan.
I'm glad.
She's cute. I'm glad.
It's so red. What do you want to see?
What do you want to see?
I don't know.
Matches?
It looks like a match.
Unique.
Like a burning flame.Like a burning flame.
It's cool.
I heard that the member colors have been announced,
I have one more thing on my mind.
I'm sure the members are wondering about it, and I'm sure the fans are wondering about it too,
What would you like to be called by the members and fans?
It's important.
I want to be called Haruka-san.
Haruka-san.
Se-no.
Se-no is good.
Can you call me that?
Se-no.
Karuizawa.
That's great.
I'm so happy.
It's too cute.
It's nice. It's very Kyoto-like.
I'm so happy.
The naming is new, too.
It's cute.
What would you like to be called, Ako-chan?
I'd like to be called Getter.
Getter.
Bow Getter.
You take it outside, don't you?
Then, can you call me again?
Getter?
Getter.
Ready.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad. This is.
I'm so happy.
Fans, please call the two of us this way.
Wait a minute.
It's okay. You'll be my seniors.
I'm a little upset. Senpai.
It's your first job.
It's cool.
Please call them both lots of names.
Please take care of them.
Thank you very much.
We are both very nervous.
So, please support Morning Musume。 23, please support us.
So, thank you very much to the two members of the 17th term.
Bye bye!
Please watch us.
Thank you. Spring is coming. Take care.
Harusan and I got it.
That's amazing.
The gap is amazing.
Hallo! Ste.
Tea Norman Maka Saito and Mika Nishizaki present "Halo! STE.
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
I will ask you some questions, so let's keep up the tempo without thinking too much.
The day after tomorrow, January 7, is Tanabata. Please tell us what you would like to write on a strip of paper.
I want to buy headphones.
Summer will soon be in full swing. What fashion items are you interested in this summer?
Chou chouSch.
Next month, the summer encore tour will be held. What would you like people to see in Mika Nishizaki?
Facial expression management
What do you always keep in mind as an idol Mika Nishizaki?
To keep a smile on my face.
Hello! Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year. Which of the past songs would you like to perform in Ochanoman?
Morning Musume。 Summer Night Town by Morning Musume。
Applause
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, I've got a question. I was wondering about something,
The wish I wanted to write on the Star Festival was to get headphones,
I have an image of Miki Nishizaki listening to music with earphones,
That's right.
Do you have a desire to switch to headphones?
Yes, of course I enjoy listening to music with earphones,
I think headphones are fun, of course, but I think that I can see a new world by putting them on with a snap,
I thought that changing the way I listen to music would add a new dimension to my enjoyment, so I wanted to get some.
What else do you want people to see in you as Miki Nishizaki?
Expression management?
Well, I'm not so sure, because I just said what came to mind,
But I think facial expressions are very important in performance, so I would like them to look at expression management.
I see.
I see. Questions for Yuko Saito will come after the VTR.
Halo! STE
Juice-Juice Pride Bright July 12, Onsah yo!
Juice-Juice Funky Forsing July 12 Onsur yo!
Juice-Juice Pride Bright July 12 Onser yo!
Juice-Juice Funky Fourth July 12 Onsah yo!
The Nippon Budokan concert was over.
It was the 25th anniversary tour,
Spring Tour SeishunrakuI was so happy that so many people came to see us.
Let's hear what Haru, the 17th term member who made her debut today, had to say.
I was very nervous before we went out, but once we went out on stage, I could see the audience plating their faces, and I really enjoyed it.
It was great.
You were smiling more than when you were doing your hair.
Next, let's see how you smile.
I laugh at myself.
It was the first time I saw the audience's faces when they sang the last song,
I was very happy to see the smiling faces of the audience, as if they were enjoying the show.
That was amazing.
You could see them from your seats.
It was the first time for the 14 of us to perform on stage together, and I hope you will look forward to seeing more performances by the 14 of us in the future.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Morning Musume。 13.
Halo! STE.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Maoho Saito.
Yes, I would like to ask her a question. I will do my best.
It's been almost a year since your medal debut. As a leader, how would you grade yourself over the past year?
75 points.
The other day, I experienced Yokohama Arena as an opening act for Angstrom. In one word, how would you describe the view you saw from there?
Spacious.
What is the key point of Maoho Saito's stage makeup?
Putting lame under the eyes.
What hairstyle would you like to try in the summer?
Half-twin hairstyle.
What would you like to do if you could perform by yourself in Hello! Project, if you could perform a beautiful song by yourself, what would it be?
Tsubaki Factory's "Just Tonight I Wanted to Float.
Thank you very much.
Now, I would like to ask you about something that has been on my mind,Well, I'd like to ask you something that has been on my mind,
What hairstyle would you like to try in the summer?
Half-twin hairstyle.
Since it's summer, I'd like to wear bright-colored clothes,
I think you will mainly wear bright-colored or stylish clothes in the summer,
I thought that if I wore a half-twin in such a situation, people would see a different Saito from usual,
I think half-twins are a good way to show a different Saito.
I would like you to wear the half-twin by all means,
I think it will be a year since Saito's major label debut, and I think he will be doing a self-assessment,
I, Saito, am quite nervous,
I have always been a little intimidated,
At first, there were many things that were really difficult to get used to.
I had a hard time getting used to it at first,
I don't give out many NGs when I shoot a video now. Little by little.
That's great.
But there are still times when I do give them out, or I bite them,
I'd like to deduct 25 points in anticipation of your future growth,
I made the score 75.
Excellent.
Shigeka Saito is a reliable leader,
I will support her to become a better leader in the future.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best to be the best leader.
There will be more to come from Halo! I'll be back soon.
This is Natsuyaki Masashi.
Now it's time for Hello Kitchen!
This time, we have this member here.
This is Honoka Kobayashi from Beyonds. I was really looking forward to today. I will do my best.
Hello, teacher, I'm looking forward to working with you today.
Yes, thank you very much.
Now then, teacher, what would you like to make this time?
Today I would like to make carrot cake.
Yay!
Carrot cake.
I love carrot cake.
Here are the ingredients for carrot cake.
Kobayashi, have you ever made carrot cake before?
I have never made carrot cake, but I had it for the first time last year and thought it was my favorite flavor.
So I am really looking forward to making it.
So let's do our best to make it today and make sure it tastes good.
I'll do my best.
So, what would you like to do first?
First of all, peel the carrots that will be the main ingredient in the lot cake.
Chop it up or grate it.
The texture will change depending on which way you do it.
Shall I grate it?
It's quite chunky and looks like this.
It's easy to eat.
First of all, peel the skin.
The head, leave it as it is.
Just the skin.
Do you usually cook, Kobayashi?
Not at all.
You don't?
Yes, in fact, I don't even cook.
Well, your mother does the basics.
That's right.
But I do make sweets for events.
Oh, I see. Valentine's Day, for example.
Are you done?
I'm going to grate it.I'm going to grate it down.
It might be easier if you do it at an angle.
I understand.
It's getting better.
Do you use another carrot? About half?
I'm using 140 or 150 grams.
That's how much I used for one carrot.
Be careful with this.
If you do this, you won't be able to play the piano anymore.
That's right, Kobayashi, you play the piano.
Beyonce, you know, everyone has their own personality.
But the piano is a very strong instrument, isn't it?
Because it's Beyonce.
I'm really happy to see you.
I'm so happy.
How is it? I've already done a lot.
I've got a lot.
It's going fast.
Next we'll use
Kurumi
Here is Miyamizu's point.
Walnuts are roasted in a frying pan to release their aroma
It's a good idea to
Slowly over low heat
over low heat.
Use 30g of walnuts
I don't use any particular oil or anything.
If you put oil on it, it's going to be different.
It's a different thing.
I want to bring out the aroma, so I kind of burn it a little bit on purpose.
It's a little bit more fragrant.
But the aroma is there, a little bit at a time.
Can you do this? Just one "f".
Oh.
Inside.
Squeeze.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's done, it's done, it's done.
Eggs with wasabi.
One egg.
Yes, 50 grams of sugar yolk.
Yolk sugar.
It smells sweet.
I see. It's sugar.
I don't think it would taste that good with regular granulated sugar.
It doesn't, does it?
Sure it does.
We'll mix it in.
Make it smooth.
What do you think of this, doctor?
Roughly.
It's all right.
It's hot, but let's chop this up.
Yes, sir.
To your liking.
I grated the carrots rather finely.
You might want to make it a little smaller.
I understand.
It smells so good.
I'll go as far as I can.
The finer you grind it...The finer you make it, the more
The finer you make it, the more walnut flavor you get.
So much carrot!
So much orange!
But it's kind of orange.
It's so cute!
It's going to be pretty, isn't it?
I'll put it in.
30 grams.
Put 30 grams.
And oil.
40g.
40 grams.
Mix it all together in close proximity.
Roughly.
It's a very rustic or simple dish.
But it has a homemade feel to it.
That's good, isn't it?
I like it that way.
Now this one.
Caking powder.
Yes, caking powder.
I often use caking powder in a sieve or something.
But in this case, it's fine.
Is it mixed?
When it's mixed
Here.
Mix it here.
Put it in.
Do you want to add salt or anything else?
Oh, you forgot the salt.
Oh, good.
Salt and a pinch of cinnamon.
A pinch.
A pinch of cinnamon.
It's all up to you, though.
It tastes better when it's fragrant.
If you like cinnamon, put a pinch of cinnamon.
Yes, a pinch of cinnamon.
Not too much?
A batch of bicorns.
You could put it in again.
The words don't match the amount.
Not even close.
Flap flap.
You're too gentle.
It's right here. Smell it.
It's so cinnamon!
If he's not here, let's have him do the bachi kong.
Wait a minute.
I can smell the cinnamon.
But I can probably smell it.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming.
Oh, my God, it's so close.
What? That's what he's saying.
I don't know, maybe he's got a weak nose.
Is he stopping for a second? Are you okay?
You want me to put a little more in there?
Just a little more bam-bam.A little more bicorne.
Just two?
I got a lot of bounces.
I'm in.
All right. - All right.
Give it a good stir.
You don't have to mix it anymore.
If you mix it too much, now...
The gluten will form.
It'll look a little different.
That's right.
It should be crunchy.
When it's mixed, it's okay.
Okay. - Okay.
That's all for now.
Let's try again next time!
See you next time!
Now it's 170 degrees Celsius for about 20 minutes
Here you go.
It tastes like a party with so many different flavors.
Well, I'm looking forward to the completion.
I'm really looking forward to it.
By the way, Mika Nishizaki, I think you were on Hello Kitchen before,
Have you done any cooking since then?
Yes, I have. I, Mika Nishizaki, made gyoza,
They were very, very well received, and I was able to make them very well.
Oh, wow.
By the way, Shigeko Saito, do you cook?
I don't cook much,
But what is your best dish?
I think my best dish is chow mein.
I think I am good at making chowan-mushi,
I would like to try making hamburgers next time.
I would like to eat both of them, so I would be happy if you could cook them for me sometime.
Please come to my house.
I am waiting for you.
Let's do it.
Hallo! Ste.
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project has a lot of songs that touched my heart,
Project has many heartbreaking songs, but I, Saito, thought that Berryz Koubou's "Otakebi Boy, Wow! Project has many heartbreaking songs, but I, Saito, thought that Berryz KOBO's song "Otakebi Boy Wow!
One of the lyrics is "I'm not the only one who's unhappy, pull your luck this way! I was in elementary school at the time,
I was in elementary school at the time,
I was in elementary school at the time, and I often felt depressed,
I was in elementary school at the time, and I often felt depressed, so I listened to this song and it gave me a lot of courage,
I was in elementary school at the time, and I often felt depressed.
How about you, Miki Nishizaki?
I, Miki Nishizaki, was a member of Ochanoma's 3rd single "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Natsu! It's the same song, but it's called "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Nattsu!
It's the same song, but it has the same lyrics, "I'm a little emotionally unstable Natsu! The title of the song is also the same as the lyrics, and the lyrics are also in the title.
It is also in the title of the song, and I put it in the lyrics as well,
I think it is a very memorable lyric,
I love the lyrics.
Now please watch the VTR.
Please watch the VTR.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Natsune Nakayama, will be presenting. Here it is!
I will walk this road. Even if it is a steep road. When we join our hearts together, something will change. The lyrics are "When we join our hearts together, something will change,
I felt that if we all work together and do our best, even if we can't do it alone, we can make our dreams come true, from the smallest to the biggest,
This lyric made me realize that we can make everything from small dreams to big dreams come true,The lyrics of this song made me realize that it is possible to achieve everything from small dreams to big dreams,
Whenever I feel a little down or troubled, I listen to this song and it scares me,
Please listen to it! Please listen to it!
It's so beautiful!
It's so beautiful! The part about reading "heart with our soul" is really nice, too.
It's true.
Yes, it is.
I'm kind of happy that they are praising us for the tea ceremony.
This song is very back-fearful, so please give it a listen.
Enjoy the next installment!
Hallo! STE!
Shigeka Saito and Mika Nishizaki of Ocha-no-Mama present "Halo! STE, presented by Shigeka Saito and Mika Nishizaki of Ochanomama.
On April 26th, the 3rd single of Ochanomama will be released!
Yay!
This single is called "Quattro Amen" and
It contains 4 songs in total!
So, I'd like to introduce the songs!
First of all, the first song is called "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer".
This song was composed by Ms. Kami Hirose, and it is a song that makes you feel very summery.
And the second one is "Ocha no Mahoroba Ikoi no Toki no Toki" (Resting Place of Tea).
The song "Showa and 2025 Wacha Wacha Wacha" is already a frightening song from the title!
I think the title of this song will already make you curious about how scary it is.
I think it's a very cool and interesting song that shows the tea as it is.
The music video also has a lot of costume changes.
Yes, that's right.
I think you can see a neo Ocha-no-Mama.
I hope you will pay attention to that as well.
And the third one, Shekenaare, as I mentioned before, is also a part of the TV anime "Shadowverse Fullui".
It is the ending song of the TV anime "Shadow Birth Full Immersion".
The lyrics include lines related to the anime, and the song is really cheerful.
It's really bright and I'm sure you can sing along with me.
Let's sing and dance together!
The fourth and last song is
The fourth and last song is "Yoridorimizuri Zuyu"!
This song has the names of fruits in the lyrics, and the choreography and the song itself are very bright and cheerful.
The choreography and the song itself is very bright and cheerful.
It is a very cute song!
Yes, please enjoy the sound single "Ocha-no-mama" to be released on July 26th!
oh oh oh oh oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
You don't know what it's like to be an adult, do you?
Can I say that?
Weekend doubts, grazed on the hip by a pick
Ping-pong is so simple.
Haribo girl.
You know, you can like that stuff.
I'm sure I'm the only one who feels that way.
Someone like that.
Listen, I'm really more of a Skylight.
Turn off the blue light and let's go have some fun.
Come on, let's get up
I wanna put my hands behind my back
Everybody wants to dance
Japan
This is the star of the show
Sasanai Koi wa Uta kara
Road
Then I can't stop swinging
My true heart's not in it
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it, Dance!
Yes, yes! The day after tomorrow is my birthday, Yamazaki Mei!Yes, yes! The day after tomorrow is my birthday!
Are you all excited?
Two new members have joined Morning Musume, and we have a new organization.
Please continue to support us.
With you in the days that are not set in stone
I want to dance as it is
I want to dance, everyone wants to dance
I'm sure
Love to you I'm not invited
Love is a bubble, if I could have it back, I'd shake it off
I can't stop the flowers from shining
I'm gonna shine
Do it!
Dance!
Come on, I can't stand up!
Come on, can't stand up!
Another chance on a bright morning Oh Yeah!
You get a chance
You get a chance again on the morning of departure Oh Yeah!
You get a chance again
I've dreamed so many times
You can't give up
Girl or boy
Hell, no more
Born on a planet I love
And I met someone I love
It's a miracle that I made it this far
With sadness and joy
Sassy phrase
Oh Yes!
All of us, if we love each other, we only live once.
To laugh or not to laugh Creepy lulaliths
Time!
Like a baby you're holding to live
Like a newborn, pure and innocent
Human beauty to like, life is just one
To laugh or not to laugh
I'm here
Life is BAD TIME
To live
Like most babies
With a pure newborn heart
That is the future
Life is to live
To the one who laughs
How many lifes
Come on! Come on! One more time!
Today and tomorrow. Every day is a 24-hour day.
Every man is wrapped up in the morning sun
Chance a ball in the dazzling morning
Oh Yeah! You get a chance
Chance a ball in the morning that takes off
Oh Yeah!
Subtitles by Keogh
Thanks to you, I can do my best
Kuboka Saito of Ocha no Ma and Miki Nishizaki of Ocha no Ma present Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement!
On July 26th, we will be releasing our 3rd single
Slightly Emotionally Unstable SummerA Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer
Tea Horse Mahorobaikoinova
Showa and 2025 are both a bit of a mess
Shekenare Yoridorimidori will be released!
These four songs are very bright and cheerful
I think they are perfect for this summer.
We hope you will listen to them a lot!
We are also holding release events all over Japan!
We would be very happy if you could come and play with us!
And from August 5th
Ocha-no-Ma Concert 2023 SUMMER
More Growing Up will start!
Yes, we hope to give you a hot performance
And I hope to show you how we have grown up again.
I will do my best, so thank you very much!
And we will perform at many idol events this summer.
We look forward to seeing you at these events as well!
Thank you very much.
Hello! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel.
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel and enjoy the new videos.
This time, I'm with Marika Saito of Ochanouma,
and Mika Nishizaki from Ochanouma.
Good bye.